=Love For Two Lives=
= الحب لعمرين =
=Episode 14=
= الحلقة 14 =
Princess.
أميرة.
We have everything you want here.
لدينا كل ما تريده هنا.
Here is a buns store.
هنا متجر الكعك.
There is a hotel.
يوجد فندق.
This restaurant you recommended is good.
هذا المطعم الذي أوصيت به جيد.
I'm glad you like it, Princess.
أنا سعيد لأنك أحببت ذلك يا أميرة.
Are you finished, Princess?
هل انتهيت يا أميرة؟
I'll go take the bill.
سأذهب لأخذ الفاتورة.
Wait, Princess.
انتظري يا أميرة.
Princess.
أميرة.
I'll pay.
سأدفع.
Okay.
تمام.
Young lady.
إمرأة شابة.
You look pretty.
تبدو جميل.
Let me go!
دعني اذهب!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Come drink with me.
تعال واشرب معي.
What am I doing?
ماذا افعل؟
I want to drink with her.
أريد أن أشرب معها.
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
You just wait there.
أنت فقط انتظر هناك.
Don't bother, Princess Xiangxiang.
لا تهتم يا الأميرة شيانغشيانغ.
General Sa is here.
الجنرال سا هنا.
He's famous for his Sa's Kungfu.
إنه مشهور بـ Sa's Kungfu.
This man will get a good thrashing.
هذا الرجل سيحصل على ضربة جيدة.
Sit down.
اجلس.
Didn't you hear?
ألم تسمع؟
General Sa.
العامة سا.
Go.
يذهب.
I will.
أنا سوف.
General Sa.
العامة سا.
Good luck.
حظا طيبا وفقك الله.
Teach him a lesson that he won't forget.
علمه درسًا لن ينساه.
I'm the general of the court,
أنا قائد المحكمة ،
General Sa.
العامة سا.
Kneel and apologize before it's too late.
اركع واعتذر قبل فوات الأوان.
Use your Kungfu.
استخدم الكونغفو الخاص بك.
Oh.
أوه.
The time is calling.
الوقت ينادي.
Wow.
رائع.
The general won.
فاز الجنرال.
General Sa.
العامة سا.
You won.
لقد فزت.
I've never seen anything like that.
لم أرَ شيئًا كهذا من قبل.
Must be a great technique.
يجب أن تكون تقنية رائعة.
What?
ماذا؟
You're taking General Sa with you?
أنت تأخذ الجنرال سا معك؟
Yes.
نعم.
There's a saying in Dongshan Kingdom. Nothing forcibly done can be agreeable.
هناك قول مأثور في مملكة دونغشان.  لا يمكن أن يكون أي شيء يُفعل بالقوة مقبولاً.
Your King does not like me.
ملكك لا يحبني.
So I won't make this hard for you.
لذلك لن أجعل هذا صعبًا عليك.
If I can marry General Sa,
إذا كان بإمكاني الزواج من الجنرال سا ،
everything happened can be forgotten.
كل ما حدث يمكن نسيانه.
No way.
مستحيل.
You can't take him with you.
لا يمكنك اصطحابه معك.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Because...
لان...
Because if you take him away,
لأنه إذا أخذته بعيدًا ،
my aunt and I will have no one in this palace.
أنا وعمتي لن يكون لدينا أحد في هذا القصر.
That's none of my concern.
هذا ليس من قلقي.
There's another saying in Dongshan...
هناك مقولة أخرى في Dongshan ...
Ay.
أوه.
I can't remember.
لا استطيع التذكر.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
he has to go with me.
عليه أن يذهب معي.
Okay.
تمام.
You can have him.
يمكنك الحصول عليه.
Aunt.
عمة.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Here.
هنا.
Congratulations on marrying the princess.
مبروك الزواج من الاميرة.
Cheers.
هتافات.
Come on.
هيا.
Yao Liangliang.
ياو ليانجليانج.
I...
أنا...
I'm so sad.
انا حزين جدا.
Stop making fun of me.
توقف عن الاستهزاء بي.
If that Princess Xiangxiang
إذا كانت تلك الأميرة شيانغشيانغ
is really
هو حقا
taking me with her
اصطحبني معها
to Dongshan Kingdom...
إلى مملكة دونغشان ...
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
I'm telling you.
أنا أخبرك.
Then I won't
ثم لن أفعل
stay in your world anymore.
ابق في عالمك بعد الآن.
I'll come back to mine.
سأعود إلى بلدي.
But...
ولكن...
What about Fei'er?
ماذا عن فيئير؟
Fei'er.
فيير.
Fei'er can stay over there.
يمكن أن يبقى فيير هناك.
I've had enough.
لقد اكتفيت.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Take your time.
خذ وقتك.
Queen.
ملكة.
I'll go for a walk.
سأذهب في نزهة على الأقدام.
See you, General Sa.
إلى اللقاء ، الجنرال سا.
Hey!
يا!
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
Come and drink more.
تعال واشرب أكثر.
Sorry for disregarding you.
آسف لتجاهلك.
I thought you said you never got drunk.
اعتقدت أنك قلت إنك لم تسكر أبدًا.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
You look pretty good today.
تبدين جميلة اليوم
I always look good.
أنا دائما أبدو بحالة جيدة.
Today,
اليوم،
you look amazing.
تبدين مذهلة.
♪Traces of time and space, and forgotten galaxies♪
آثار الزمان والمكان ، والمجرات المنسية
♪Time alternates our relationship♪
الوقت يتناوب علاقتنا ♪
♪The sea of stars is pretty and quiet♪
♪ بحر النجوم جميل وهادئ
♪The rain touches the breath♪
المطر يمس النفس ♪
♪Get close to you♪
♪ اقترب منك
♪Watch the skyline♪
♪ مشاهدة الأفق ♪
♪Touch the starry night♪
♪ المس الليل المرصع بالنجوم ♪
♪At this moment♪
♪ في هذه اللحظة ♪
♪We look for love♪
♪ نبحث عن الحب ♪
♪The time mixed everything up♪
الوقت مختلط كل شيء
♪This is when I fall in love♪
♪ هذا عندما أقع في الحب ♪
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Hmm.
همم.
♪I met you♪
♪ التقيت بك ♪
It's great.
إنه لشيء رائع.
Don't marry other people.
لا تتزوج من أشخاص آخرين.
♪I woke up surprised♪
♪ استيقظت متفاجئًا ♪
♪I met you♪
♪ التقيت بك ♪
♪I fell in love♪
♪ وقعت في الحب ♪
♪It was yesterday♪
♪ كان البارحة
♪I want to see your eyes♪
♪ اريد ان ارى عينيك ♪
♪When I wake up♪
♪ عندما أستيقظ
♪You are not here♪
♪ أنت لست هنا
♪Traces of time and space, and forgotten galaxies♪
آثار الزمان والمكان ، والمجرات المنسية
♪Time alternates our relationship♪
الوقت يتناوب علاقتنا ♪
♪The sea of stars is pretty and quiet♪
♪ بحر النجوم جميل وهادئ
♪The rain touches the breath♪
المطر يمس النفس ♪
♪Get close to you♪
♪ اقترب منك